Khaled Yousef Abu-Fannas

Kha2000.khaled@Gmail.com · +962 796911282 12-3-2000 . Single . Amman-Jordan

Computer Science fresh graduate with good knowledge with multiple programming languages, web development, problem solving, customer service and content moderator. I always have passion to learn new technologies and improve my quick learning skills. I am knee to find a workplace that I can apply my knowledge and experience.

EXPERIENCE

1/2024 - 4/2024

Content Moderator, Webhelp

Responsible for reviewing and monitoring all users content that violates any standards and policies of an online platform.

6/2022 - 9/2022

JR Customer support and data entry officer , Lavishride (online)

Responsible for the customers support by replying on their inquires and helping the using the company's app and site.

6/2021 - 2/2022

Freelancer, Web development

6/2019 - 11/2019

Crew Trainer, McDonald's

Train new crew members and ensure items are well stocked, also making sure that food safety rules are followed, and monitoring employee performance.

EDUCATION

6/2022

Computer Science Bachelor's, BAU

Graduated with Good degree.

8/2018

High school, Al-Qassim School

Scientific section (81).

TRAINING COURSES

```
11/2023
Object Oriented JavaScript , Online – Udacity.

6/2023
Node.js Crash Course , Online – Udacity.

11/2022
Intro to JavaScript , Online – Udacity.

2/2022
Version control with get , Online – Coursera.

2/2020
Customer centric culture , Amman – BePro.
```

SKILLS

- Computer and Internet
- Work under pressure
- Communication skills
- Teamwork

- Gaming
- Quick learner
- Microsoft office
- Problem Solving

LANGUAGES

Arabic (Reading, Writing, Speaking) Mother tongue.

English (Reading, Writing, Speaking) Very good.